Guide to the Leon F. Litwack Collection of Berkeley, California, Protest Literature
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Files, Series I; 4; (4 boxes)
  - File 5 (Box 1, Folder 9-11)
    - UC, Academic Senate. Resolution with arguments. Nov 3, 1969. Blue paper.
  - File 6 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Ad hoc Committee of Concerned Students (org). WHERE IS REASON? Flyer, yellow paper
    - AFL-CIO. UNION SUMMER. Poster in colors. 1998.
    - American Students for Israel (org). THE SABOTAGE ORGANIZATIONS AND THE NAZIS. Flyer.
    - Campus Draft Opposition (org). VIETNAM COMMENCEMENT. May 17 (no year) Flyer, light blue paper.
    - Christian World Liberation Front (org) AND AFTER THIS WAR? Flyer, green paper.
    - Christian World Liberation Front (org) AND AFTER THIS WAR? Flyer, yellow/orange paper.
    - Christic Institute (org) BEHIND THE IRAN / CONTRA AFFAIR:, flyer, 4pp.
    - Cleaver (Kathleen) SEX, LIES & VIDEOTAPE / Researching the History of the Black Panther Party. Poster. University of California, Berkeley. Wheeler Hall lecture (nd)
    - Free Speech Movement (org). HAPPINESS IS AN ACADEMIC SENATE MEETING. Flyer, blue paper.
    - Fruehan (George J.) = senior, University of California, Berkeley. SOLUTION OR DIVERSION? Flyer.
    - Jackson (Jesse) DEAR FRIEND = [open letter]. Washington, DC, 1988. Campaigning. 4pp.
    - Legal Aid Fund. Contribution mailer, to Jeremiah Stamler, Chicago. Yellow paper.
    - McCarthy For President Dinner Committee, ticket reservation card
    - Movement for a Democratic Military (MDM) (org). GIS CAN STOP THE WAR. Angela Davis spoke. Flyer, legal size. Fort Ord map, verso. For March 16, 1970.
    - Oakland 7 (org). WITH A LITTLE HELP FROM OUR FRIENDS. Flyer on behalf of the Oakland 7. March 17, 1969. The Oakland 7 were anti-war protestors (members of the Campus [UC Berkeley] Stop the Draft Week Committee) arrested on October 17, 1967 at the Oakland, California induction center during Stop the Draft Week protest activities. The defendants were charged on January 28, 1969 by the Oakland Grand Jury with conspiracy to commit misdemeanors.
    - Peoples Park Negotiation Committee (org). WHERE WE STAND. For June 4
    - Saturday Review, June 21, 1969. Offprint. POWER TO THE PEOPLE. Small yellow sheet, signed B. B. S.
    - STATEMENT BY CHANCELLOR HEYNS. Flyer.
    - Student Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam (SMC) (org). IT MUST ENDWE CAN FIND IT!. Flyer. For April 21 [1970]
    - UA (org) JOIN US IN THE FIGHT FOR STUDENT DIGNITY. Folded flyer, student electioneering.
    - Union for Radical Political Economics (org) WHATS LEFT: Radical Social Science at UCB. Spring 1982 flyer.
    - Universities Committee on the Problems of War and Peace of Greater New York. Mailer, 2pp.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Committee on University Welfare. Resolution to deliberate questions and to report. 1p.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Faculty Members. A MESSAGE ON THE PROPOSED SOLUTION TO THE FREE SPEECH CONTROVERSY. 1964. 4pp.
    - Voters Pledge (org). Campaign mailer, California headquarters.
    - WELCOME TO BERKELEY. Flyer. Map, incl. Peoples Park, Insurrection City, Provo Park, Bail Fund/Free Church; ACLU; Free University of Berkeley; Pigs locations (3) = police. Flyer.
  - File 7 (Box 1, Folder 13-15)
    - AF of T (org) EXTRAORDINARY CONVOCATION OF THE UNIVERSITY COMMUNITY / / DEFEND THE SUSPENDED STUDENTS.
    - Agricultural Labor Support Committee (org). CHRISTMAS GREETINGS FROM DELANO. Includes a printed letter from Cesar Chavez.
    - Amendment to End the War [org]. HAS THE PRESIDENT COMMITTED AMERICAN TROOPS TO AN ILLEGAL WAR?
    - American Association of University Professors, Berkeley Chapter (org). Dear Colleague = open letter from Bernard L. Diamond, President. December 14, 1966
    - American Association of University Professors, Berkeley Chapter (org). Dear Chancellor Heyns = open letter from Bernard L. Diamond, President. December 8, 1966
    - ANOTHER STUDENT FOR PEACE. LA: Aldine Co. for Another Mother For Peace (org) (nd). Bumper sticker in orange and black, illustrated.
    - ARE YOU CONCERNED.
    - ASUC Strike Coordinating Committee (org). THINGS YOU CAN DO TO HELP. Pink stock.
    - ASUC: Committee for Fiscal Responsibility (org). STOP THE FREEZE INITIATIVE. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 1 June 1967]
    - Bank of America (org) BANK OF AMERICA COMMENTS ON: Academic Freedom / Students Rights / The Rhetoric of Revolutionaries. Excerpts from A. W. Clausens remarks (Oresident, Bank of America). 4pp.
    - Bay Area GI-CLDC (org). CELEBRATE THE VICTORY OF OUR G.I BROTHERS / the Ft. Jackson 8. Illustrated.
    - Berkeley Anti-Draft Union / Wesley Foundation. (org). SUMMER CALL-UPS.
    - Black Panther Party (in part) / (org) / East Bay Mobilization (org). OAKLAND SPEAKS. Illus. Rally call.
    - Black Panther Party (org). INTRODUCING ELDRIDGE CLEAVER. 4pp. Tuesday July 2, Cleaver appearance at University of California, Berkeley. Leaflet.
    - Black Panther Party / Huey Newton Defense Fund. 8pp, reproducing legal doc. November 23, 1967.
    - Black Panther Party. NY Times clipping article (not valued, but included). Feb 4/Feb 5.
    - Bond (Julian) DEAR FRIENDS = open letter, February 1967.
    - BRING ALL THE TROOPS HOME NOW. Nov. 14. Vietnam Moratorium. Berkeley Graphic Arts poster. Yellow paper.
    - Campus Community for New Politics (org). COME TO THE MARCH. Illustrated. Yellow-orange stock.
    - Campus Friends of Free University of Berkeley (org). FREE UNIVERSITY OF BERKELEY / Counter Course Project.
    - Campus International Socialists (org) WHERE DO WE GO FROM HERE. Light tan stock.
    - CCO / distributed by AFT Local #1570 (orgs). LE ROI SAMUSE
    - Chavez (Cesar) Membership card, Professors Academic Membership 1966, NATIONAL FARM WORKERS ASSOCIATION / Delano, Calif. Signed by Chavez. This program to enroll support for the farm workers among the academic community was funneled in part through Professor Leon Litwack at University of California, Berkeleyerkeley. Signed by Chavez.
    - Christmas Eve Vigil Committee, Berkeley (org). CHRISTMAS EVE VIGIL. Yellow stock.
    - CITED STUDENTS UNION (org). HERE WE STAND. Folded leaflet.
    - Civil Action Day Committee (org) WHY WE MUST COMMIT DIVIL DISOBELIENCE NOW. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 8 June 67
    - Civil Action Day Committee (org. DIRECT ACTION AGAINST THE WAR. June 29th Oakland Induction Center. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 5 June 67.
    - Clergy and Laymen Concerned About Vietnam (org). I SENT THEM A GOOD BOY AND THEY MADE HIM A MURDERER!
    - Committee for the Establishment of Community = C.E.C. LISTEN. Pale yellow stock.
    - Committee of Concerned Asian Scholars (org) CCAS SPEAKERS NOTES, 8pp. May 8, 1970.
    - Coordinating Committee / Berkeley Chapter (org). NOON RALLY. Docketed:[Sproul] Plaza handout 26 May 1967.
    - COPS ON CAMPUS / STRIKE.
    - Congress on Racial Equality (CORE) (org) CORE MOVES DOWNTOWN. Yellow stock.
    - Direct Action Committee / Alameda County Peace and Freedom Movement (org). NO JUSTICE! / Demonstrate at Huey Newtons ArraignmentFeb. 13
    - Downtown Coalition (org). DOWNTOWN PEACE COALITION / DECLARATION OF PURPOSE AND PRINCIPLES.
    - Educators for Social Responsibility (org). EAST BAY UPDATE. Yellow stock. 8pp, with insert on orange paper: BACK FROM THE USSR.
    - END THE ARMS RACE NOT THE HUMAN RACE. Folded purple and white bumper sticker.
    - FREE DEBRAY. Yellow stock. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 21 Nov 67.
    - Free University of Berkeley (org). Free Speech Movement / What Good Does It Do? Friday, November 11. Illustrated. Folded flyer.
    - FREEDOM OF SPEECH / CALL FOR ENTRIES / Berkeley Art Project. Large folded black, yellow and white poster, illustrated. Designed by Deborah Seidman.
    - Friends Committee on Legislation of Northern California (org). Dear Friend = open letter, December 6, 1966
    - Fund for Peace (auspices of this org). SECOND NATIONAL CONVENTION ON THE CHALLENGE OF BUILDING PEACE. Advisory Council named.
    - Fund for Peace (auspices of this org). SECOND NATIONAL CONVENTION ON THE CHALLENGE OF BUILDING PEACE Statement of Purpose. 4pp.
    - GI-CIVILIAN MARCH. Easter Sunday April 6.
    - Group for Student Participation = GSP (org). THIS CONCERNS YOU. Yellow stock. Docketed:[Sproul] Plaza handout 29 May 1967.
    - Group for Student Participation = GSP (org). VOTE NOW / VOTE YES!. Yellow stock. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 1 June 67.
    - Group for Student Participation = GSP (org). WHAT DOES IT TAKE. Docketed:[Sproul] Plaza handout 31 May 1967.
    - Group for Student Participation = GSP (org). NOTICE. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 2 June 67.
    - Heyns (Roger W.) Chancellor, University of California, Berkeley. Open letter to the Berkeley Community, November 19, 1967. On student suspensions.
    - IM A BETTER AMERICAN THAN YOU ARE. Small oblong poster in red, white and blue.
    - Lawyers Constitutional Defense Committee (org). THE LAW (reprint from Time, August 16, 1968)
    - Lawyers Constitutional Defense Committee of the Roger Baldwin Foundation of ACLU, Inc (org). DEAR FRIENDS = open letter from Julian Bond.
    - LET WORLD-DISARMAMENT BE YOUR SHELTER. Bumper sticker
    - LETTER OF TRANSMITTAL TO PRESIDENT JOHNSON (June 22, 1966) Signed in type by various distinguished figures, including novelist William Eastlake.
    - Los Angeles Times, Friday, June 23, 1967. Section containing AN OPEN LETTER TO PRESIDENT JOHNSON AND THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY. Newsprint, 8pp in all.
    - M. L. KING JUNIOR HIGH / BERKELEY / A Dream of School. Illustrated bumper sticker. Albany: The Albany Press (nd). Bumper sticker.
    - MARCXH ON SACRAMENTO, Saturday February 11th. Faculty endorsed demonstration. Pale green stock, folded. With map.
    - November 14 Strike Committee (org). STRIKE! NOV. 14 FOR IMMEDIATE WITHDRAWAL illustrated. On pink stock.
    - PEOPLES COALITION. Pink stock.
    - PEOPLES COALITION. Yellow stock.
    - RECERTIFY HISTORY AND INSTITUTION COURSES! Illustrated by Bowker.
    - S.F. Mime Troupe (org). CANCELLED(illustrated).
    - SDS / War Complicity Committee / Campus. HEYNS DOES IT 57 WAYS (ref to Chancellor Heyns, punning on food makers advertising.
    - SDS. PUERTO RICAN STUDENTS SMASH ROTC. Yellow stock.
    - Seminarians from the Graduate Theological Union: Berkeley (org) THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES HAS ILLEGALLY SENT AMERICAN = first line. Faded mimeo.
    - SOME PEOPLE DONT LIKE TO HEAR NEW POINTS OF VIEW Illustrated. Berkeley Litho Service. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 25 May 1967.
    - SPEING MOBILIZATION COMMITTEE TO END THE WAR IN VIETNAM. (org). Open letter from Edward M. Keating, January 14, 1967, to Dear friends
    - STATEMENT BY FACULTY WITNESSES WITH RESPECT TO NOVEMBER 30, 1966. 4pp. Differs from the University of California, Berkeley administrations view and accounts of the events
    - STRIKE TO END THE WA / FRIDAY. Stop the Murder in Southeast Asia and at Home. Light tan stock.
    - Student Mobilization Committee (org). CAMPUS MOBILIZER illustrated. 12pp, including blue insert.
    - Student Mobilization Committee (org). GIS DIEAS NIXON LIES TO THE PEOPLE.
    - Student Mobilization Committee c/o WOMEN FOR PEACE (org). Dear Friend = open letter. January 13, 1967.
    - Student Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam (Berkeley) (org). URGENT-SMC NEEDS YOUR HELP.
    - Sunflower Fund (org). THE SUNFLOWER [MS.] STORY: A Chance for Change National Committee for Free Elections in Sunflower. [Black political activism].
    - Susskind (Charles) professor of Electrical Engineering, University of California, Berkeleyerkeley. REMARKS at the meeting of the academic senate, Dec 5, 1966. 2pp.
    - TET FAST FOR PEACE / GRACE CATHEDRAL. Yellow stock printed in red and black.
    - THE OPERATION IN CAMBODIA WILL SAVE AMERICAN LIVES.
    - THE STREETS OF OUR COUNTRY ARE IN TURMOIL Stenciled red lettering, Hitlers speech quoted ton present purpose. Repeated verso.
    - U.P.B. (org) SUN BEAR will speak. Illustrated. Docketed: [Sproul] Plaza handout 29 May 1967.
    - U.S. OUT OF CAMBODIA / STOP THE WAR IN SOUTHEAST ASIA. Illus. Blue stock.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Academic Senate (org). MEETINGTuesday March 7, 1967. 17pp report.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Academic Senate (org). NOTICE OF MEETING / SPECIAL MEETING called for Tuesday, October 14, 1969. Blue stock.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Academic Senate (org). TO THE MEMBERS OF THE BERKELEY DIVISION. Signed in type by various professors.
    - University of California, Berkeleyerkeley (org). University Bulletin 15:38 (May 22, 1967) [for Staff of University of California, Berkeley]
    - University of California, Berkeleyerkeley (org). University Bulletin 15:40 (June 5, 1967) [for Staff of University of California, Berkeley]
    - University of California, Berkeleyerkeley. Academic Senate. Minutes. December 5 and 8, 1966
    - University of California, Berkeleyerkeley. Academic Senate. Minutes. January 10 and 17,1967
    - University of California, Berkeleyerkeley. Academic Senate. Minutes. January 24, 1967
    - University of California, Berkeleyerkeley. Academic Senate. Minutes. November 8, 1966
    - University of California, Berkeleyerkeley. Academic Senate. Minutes. October 17 and 20, 1966
    - Unitas, Newman Hall and Hillel (Berkeley orgs). VIETNAM MORATORIUM. Green stock.
    - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA POLICIES RELATING TO STUDENTS AND STUDENT ORGANIZATIONS, UNE OF UNIVERSITY FACILITIES, AND NONDISCRIMINATION.
    - VIETNAM MORATORIUM. Oct 15. Green paper. Berkeley Graphic Arts.
    - WALLACE. Eagle illustration. Bumper sticker in red, white and blue.
    - WAR OR PEACE. Bahaullah document.
    - War Resisters League (org) RESIST WAR TAXES.
    - War Tax Resistance (org). WAR TAX RESISTANCE. Quotes Allen Ginsberg at length, 1969. 6pp.
    - WE WORK FOR PEACE / L-D. peel-back sticker, dove image in blue and white
    - Workers for Peoples Democracy (org). ONE EXAMPLE OF THE WIDE SPREAD CONTROL OF TECHNOCRATIC THOUGHT = first line.
    - YOUR EARTH / NO DEPOSITY / NO RETURN? Bumper sticker in yellow and black.
  - File 8 (Box 1, Folder 16-19)
    - AFT 1474 = Berkeley Faculty Union, AFT 1474 (org) REPORT, 3pp.
    - AFT 1474 = University Federation of Teachers AFT Local 1474 (org.) REPORT / California Senate Concurrent Resolutions
    - American Association of University Professors (org). Chapter meeting, Friday, October 30. University of California, Berkeley. 7pp.
    - American Committee for the Fourth International (et al) (orgs). FREE ADOLFO GILLY! [Argentine Marxist].
    - American Historical Association (org) and the Organization of American Historians (org) ANNOUNCE THE FORMATION OF THE JOINT COMMITTEE FOR THE DEFENSE OF THE RIGHTS OF HISTORIANS UNDER THE FIRST AMENDMENT. With cover letter, July 22, 1966.
    - American Writers Congress (org). PROGRAM, NYC, Oct 9-12, 1981, with attached questionnaire, 79pp.
    - August 6-9 Committee for the International Days of Protest (org). WE DEMAND FREEDOM FOR G.I.S. Red and black printing.
    - Bay Area Agenda (org). DEAR FRIEND = open letter STATEMENT OF PURPOSE.
    - Berkeley Student Mobilization Committee (org). TALK IS CHEAP. Illus. (duplicate?)
    - Berkeley Student Mobilization Committee. TALK IS CHEAPO lllustrated.
    - Black Pnther Party (org) COME SEE ABOUT HUEY / MAY DAY MASS RALLY. Red ink on light tan stock.
    - C.P.E. & S. F. Newsreel (orgs) PRERSENT: FILMS: Columbia Revolt & 199X. Illustrated from photograph by Nacio Jan Brown.
    - CALL TO THE BERKELEY CAMPUS TO MOBILIZE FOR THE IMMEDIATE WITHDRAWAL OF US TROOPS FROM VIET NAM March date: Saturday April 15
    - Campus Committee for New Politics (org). THE SMILING FACE OF THE LIBERAL ESTABLISHMENT. Illustrated.
    - Campus Draft Opposition (org) HONOR AND SUPPORT MEN WHO RESIST THE DRAFT Friday May 17. Red printing on yellow stock
    - Campus Draft Opposition (org). FORUM ON IMMIGRATION TO CANADA.
    - Campus Mobilization (org). MOBILIZATION GENERAL MEMBERSHIP MEETING April 6 (illustrated)
    - Campus Mobilization Committee (org) MARCH ON APRIL 15 TO OPPOSE THE WAR. Illustrated.
    - Campus Mobilization Committee (org). A CALL TO VIETNAM WEEK. Illustrated.
    - Campus Mobilization Committee (org). DEAR FACULTY MEMBER = open letter signed in print by Jean Savage
    - Cheit (Earl F.) Executive Vice-President, University of California, Berkeley. STATEMENT. November 30, 1966. 2pp.
    - Citizen (Berkeley) Vol 1:1 (pre-publication issue), 4pp.
    - CITIZENS FOR A VOTE ON VIETNAM (org). DEAR FRIEND = open letter
    - CNP (org). AND AFTER FINALS WHAT?.... illustrated, golded.
    - Coalition News 3:5 (March 12, 1969)
    - Committee of Concerned Students (ad hoc org). WHERE IS REASON? Yellow stock.
    - Committee on Statement on Freedom of Dissent and Resistance (ad hoc org). DEAR SIGNER= open letter, April 24, 1968. 9pp.
    - Congress of Racial Equality. DEAR FRIEND= open letter signed in print by Floyd B. McKissick, National Director.
    - Cordier (Dr. Andrew W.) DEAR FRIEND= open letter, December 7, 1967.
    - DEAR COLLEAGUE signed by 12 UC Professors. Call to rally and march. SUPPORT THE APRIL 15 DEMONSTRATION.
    - DICK LORD FOR CONGRESS 4th DISTRICT/ Democrat. Open letter personalized to Leon Litwack, from Finance Chairman Gene Rupel.
    - Disarmament Resource Center (org). DEAR FRIEND = open letter with attachments
    - Downtown Coalition (org) DOWNTOWN PEACE COALITION ALL DAY RALLY / Friday, Nov. 14. Pale blue stock, blue lettering.
    - East Bay Student Mobilization Committee to End the War in Southeast Asia (or) LOS ANGELES WAS PICKED TO BE THE SITE OF THE WEST COAST NATIONAL ACTION BECAUSE= first line.
    - Faculty Peace Committee + Campus Ministry (orgs). Invite PRIVATE RONALD LOCKMAN cocktail reception / petition movement (black soldier resists)
    - Franklin (Benjamin) RULES BY WHICH A GREAT EMPIRE MAY BE REDUCED TO A SMALL ONE 2pp, mimeo.
    - Freedman (David A.) = Associate Professor of Statistics; member of the Student Affairs Committee, University of California, Berkeley. A MINORITY REPORT January 6, 1967. 8pp.
    - Graham (Hugh Davis) = Assistant Professor of History, Stanford University. COLLEAGUES = open letter
    - Gray (John A., Jr.) junior, University of California, Berkeley. IT MAY WELL BE THAT THE CURRENT DISTURBANCES IN OPINION = first line. 9 pages (rectos only).
    - Harris (Dicky) for the RESISTANCE. WERE TURNING IN OUR COP-OUTS.
    - HELP END THE WAR / Telegraph Ave (Berkeley) PEACE FAIR.
    - Heyns (Roger W.) = Chancellor, University of California, Berkeley. A STATEMENT (soiled, old fold). I am opposed to the strike Undated.
    - Heyns (Roger W.) = Chancellor, University of California, Berkeley. A STATEMENT (soiled, old fold). I am opposed to the strike Reformatted, dated December 5, 1966
    - I DONT Red, white and blue designed card.
    - King (Martin Luther, Jr.) DEAR FRIEND = open letter, October 1966, for SCLC (org)
    - Liberal Democrat V:3 (December 1964)
    - Lockman Defense Committee (org). HELL NO, I WONT GO (Ronald Lockman) black private in Army
    - MacLeish (Archibald) American poet. DEAR FRIEND= open letter dated September 1967. Gray stock, 2pp.
    - MEET RON LOCKMAN / A [black] Soldier Who Says No to War (photograph reproduced).
    - NATIONAL ANTI-DRAFT DAY IS WEDBESDAY, JUNE 10. Poster for rallying, resisting, demonstrating, from the Peace Brigade & Resistance.
    - NATION-WIDE STRIKE. Yellow-orange stock. In re USAs invasion of Cambodia.
    - Naval; Air Station Training Unit (org) DEAR SIR = open letter NOON RALLY FRIDAY
    - New Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam (org). STOP IT. Rally call. Illus. for a march on Nov. 15. There are least two flyers headed thus, similar but not identical.
    - New Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam (org) STOP IT / Immediate and Total Withdrawal from Vietnam. Illustrated.
    - New Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam (org). STOP IT / Immediate and Total Withdrawal from Vietnam. Rally call. Illus. There are least two flyers headed thus, similar but not identical.
    - No Tax For War Committee (org). AN OPEN LETTER with SOME METHODS OF NON PAYMENT (two pieces)
    - No Tax for War Committee. NO INCOME TAX FOR WAR. March 11, 1967.
    - Northern California Peace Coalition (org). MARCH AGAINST THE WAR / Los Angeles April 22. Purple ink, illustrated.
    - One World Family / Messiahs World Crusade (org[s]). THIS MAN (Nixon) CANT MAKE UP HIS MIND..TO END THE WAR IN VIETNAM / CAN YOU?
    - Pentagon Papers Fund, Inc. (org) DEAR FRIEND= open letter. Illustrated from photograph.
    - Peoples Park issue, Berkeley, CA. SOD, BROTHERS. Pink stock, legal-size.
    - Peoples Park Negotiating Committee (org). TO THE PARK / TORCH LIGHT PARADE. EXORCISE THE DEVILS on verso.
    - PORT CHICAGOS WHERE THE ACTION IS (sponsored by various orgs). Rally call for August 7.
    - Rabkin (Norman) Associate Dean for Faculty and Student Relations. University of California, Berkeley. TO: Faculty of the College of Letters and Science, with enclosures. April 1, 1969. 3pp.
    - SCLC (org). THE SCLC SAGA IN GRENADA, MISS.
    - SDS (University of California, Berkeley campus). SUPPORT YANK-FIGHT REPRESSION!
    - SDS (University of California, Berkeleyerkeley division) (org). FIGHT RACIST U.C. BOSSES!
    - SDS of Northern California (org). NO MORATORIUM ON FIGHTING IMPERIALISM-SUPPORT G. E. STRIKERS.
    - SOME OF THE ACTIONS TAKEN BY THE FACULTY ON OTHER CAMPUSES OF THE UNIVERSITY
    - Strike Committee (org). A CHRONOLOGY OF THE EVENTS OCCURING IN THE LOWER LOBBY, BETWEEN THE ENTRANCES TO THE BEARS LAIR AND THE ASUC BOOKSTORE, DURING THE AFTERNOON OF WEDNESDAY, DECEMBER 30, 1966. 14pp.
    - STRIKE NOWFLUNK LATER
    - Student Government Strike Committee (org). ARE YOU CONCERNED?
    - Student Mobilization Committee (SMC) (org). DEAR FRIEND= open letter
    - Student Mobilization Committee BUILD THE FALL OFFENIVE AGAINST THE WAR. Illustrated.
    - Student Mobilization Committee. BAY AREA NATIONAL MEETING FOR THE KENT STATE MARTYRS. May 8.
    - Sun Reporter Supplement. SF, November 15, 1969. END THE WAR IN VIETNAM / NEW MOBILIZATION WEST. Newsprint, 4pp (illustrated).
    - THE DEMISE OF FREEDOM. Yellow-orange stock.
    - THERE WILL BE A CURFEW IN BERKELEY, INCLUDING THE CAMPUS, BEGINNING AT 8:00 P.M. TONIGHT. July 1, 1968.
    - UC Clerical, Technical and Professional Employees Union (org). NO BUSINESS AS USUAL / UC EMPLOYEES SUPORT THE MORATORIUM. Blue stock.
    - UC-=Berkeley. Office of the Chancellor. STATEMENT by Chancellor Roger W. Heyns. May 29, 1969.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Academic Senate. Record of the Assembly, Vol VI:3 (May 19, 1969)
    - University of California, Berkeley. Depy of History. To Members of the Department. Notice from Nicholas V. Rissanovsky, Chairman. March 3, 1969.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Office of the Chancellor. STATEMENT by Chancellor Roger W. Heyns. April 7, 1969, 1p.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Office of the Chancellor. STATEMENT by Vice Chancellor Robert L. Johnson. April 4, 1969. 2pp.
    - University of California, Berkeleyerkeley, Academic Senate. Meeting, Monday, April 7, 1969. REPORT. 5pp.
    - University of California, Berkeleyerkeley, Academic Senate. MEETING, Tuesday, May 66pp.
    - University of California, Berkeleyerkeley, Academic Senate. Minutes. March 4, 1969.
    - University of California, Berkeleyerkeley. Academic Senate (org). Dec. 8, 1964. 17pp, illustrated.
    - University of California, Berkeleyerkeley. Department of History. TO THE FACULTY. May 21, 1969. Blue stock.
    - United Committee Against the War. (Berkeley org). UNITED COMMITTEE MEETING.
    - University Bulletin 17:29 (March 31, 1969).